[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor said the popular line Mama always said life was like a box of chocolates. You never know what youre gonna get in an Oscar-winning 1994 movie?", "correct_answer": "Tom Hanks", "incorrect_answers": ["Sean Penn", "Leonardo DiCaprio", "Dustin Hoffman"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Despite its name, the movie Sweet Home Alabama was actually filmed in many small towns in Louisiana.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which former NFL running back played the sheriff  in the Western classic 100 Rifles?", "correct_answer": "Jim Brown", "incorrect_answers": ["Alan Ameche", "Jim Taylor", "OJ Simpson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these mollusks is able to glide over in air for up to 50 meters (164 feet)?", "correct_answer": "Squid", "incorrect_answers": ["Oyster", "Octopus", "Slug"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "On May 5, 1961, this man became the first U.S. astronaut in space.", "correct_answer": "Alan Shepard", "incorrect_answers": ["Buzz Aldrin", "Neil Armstrong", "John Glenn"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Do you know what TCP stands for?", "correct_answer": "Transmission Control Protocol", "incorrect_answers": ["Transfer Control Protocol", "Time Control Protocol", "Turbo Connection Protocol"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Star Wars character General Grievous is always accompanied by 2 magna guards.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the origin of the word yogurt?", "correct_answer": "Turkish", "incorrect_answers": ["Hebrew", "Latin", "Greek"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Vitamin B2 has which of these interesting properties?", "correct_answer": "It is fluorescent under UV light.", "incorrect_answers": ["It is can be absorbed only through the skin.", "It can be found in all three physical conditions of matter.", "It melts at more than 10 000 degrees C."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What part of your body becomes a connection method when colored?", "correct_answer": "Bluetooth", "incorrect_answers": ["Green tongue", "Blond hair", "Red-eye"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "You Only Live Twice, Ian Flemings twelfth novel, was adapted as the fifth entry in the James Bond movie series by what screenplay writer, famous for his childrens books?", "correct_answer": "Roald Dahl", "incorrect_answers": ["Lee Cronin", "D.C. Fontana", "Samuel A. Pepys"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the last state to put photos on drivers licenses?", "correct_answer": "New York", "incorrect_answers": ["New Jersey", "Hawaii", "Alaska"]}]